http://www.dlilearn.com/privacy-policy/

Our Commitment To Privacy
Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available on our homepage and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.
The Information We Collect
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on the website. On some pages, you can make requests, and register to receive materials. The types of personal information collected at these pages are:
Name
Address
Email address
Phone number
Website
Company Name
Referred By
The Way We Use Information
We use the information you provide about yourself when placing an order only to complete that request for information. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to complete that process.
We use return email addresses to answer the email we receive. Such addresses are not used for any other purpose and are not shared with outside parties.
You can register with our website if you would like to receive our newsletter as well as updates on our new products and services. Information you submit on our website will not be used for this purpose unless you fill out the applicable registration form.
We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals.
Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
Our Commitment To Data Security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How You Can Access Or Correct Your Information
You can inquire about all your personally identifiable information that we collect online and maintain by contacting us. We use this procedure to better safeguard your information.
You can correct factual errors in your personally identifiable information by sending us a request that credibly shows error.
To protect your privacy and security, we will also take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.
Lucky Orange Web Analytics Service
This site uses the Lucky Orange analytics system to help improve usability and the customer experience. Lucky Orange may record mouse clicks, mouse movements and scrolling activity. Lucky Orange may record keystroke information that you voluntarily enter on this website. Lucky Orange does not track this activity on any site that does not use the Lucky Orange system. You can choose to disable the Lucky Orange Service at http://www.luckyorange.com/disable.php. Note, that doing so will disable other features of the Lucky Orange system that this site employs such as 1-to-1 support chat.
Locations St. Albans (HQ)
2 Champlain Commons, Suite 7St. Albans, VT 05478
(802) 528-5011
Burlington
1 Lawson Lane, Suite 340Burlington, VT 05401
(802) 662-1885
Learn more about us
Learn what clients say about us
BlogSome Spotify Users Reporting Possible Hacking Of Their AccountDecember 9th, 2020The 2014 Home Depot Data Breach Finally Reaches SettlementDecember 8th, 2020New Scam Lures Victims With Promise Of Federal AssistanceDecember 7th, 2020Company Since 1999, Vermont Connections has been a leading provider of IT support and consulting, focusing on businesses in New England & New York. We have helped hundreds of businesses increase productivity and profitability by making IT a streamlined part of operations.
We equip our clients with customized technology solutions for greater operational value and to reduce risk.
FacebookLinkedInYouTube
Proud Member of
Learn more about us
Learn what clients say about us
© Copyright 2020 Vermont Connections
Privacy Policy
Get Pricing Straight To Your Inbox
Let Us Know What Your IT Needs Are And Get A Quote.
Enter Your Information To Get Your PricingName*
First
Last
Email*
Company*What IT Solutions Do You Need?*- Select One -Managed IT ServicesBusiness ContinuityEmail ProtectionCloud ServicesCyber SecurityVoIP ServicesManaged Remote StrategyTell Us About Your IT ChallengesEmailThis field is for validation purposes and should be left unchanged.
X
